# Or Zarhi

# Full-Stack Developer

### **About Me**

I'm an experienced software developer with 2 years of experience in the industry and a deep passion for programming. Throughout my career, I'm always looking for ways to improve my skills and stay on top of the latest technologies.

### **Experience**

### **Full-Stack Developer**

Maxsoft company Aug 2022 to present A Full Stack Developer at a professional software company. Worked on several projects for various customers. Developed and maintained code with assorted tools, such as: Node.js, .NET, mongoDB, Sql, JavaScript and React.

#### **Computer Science Tutor**

Zefat College

Jan 2023 to present

Teaching C#, Data structures and Algorithms courses. Letter of recommendation

#### **Full-Stack Developer**

Codeo company

Jun 2021 to Jul 2022

I worked as Full Stack Developer, developed and maintained code, and had the chance to work with: Node.js, .NET, JavaScript and React.

### **Education**

### **Kinneret College**

Nov 2019 to Jun 2023

#### **Practical Software Engineer Student**

93 GPA

### **Skills**

Node.js, Express.js, .NET, RESTful, MVC, Git, SQL, NoSQL, HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Remix

## **Military Service**

#### **Division 319**

Feb 2016 to Oct 2018

I managed other soldiers, took care of orders and supplies.

### Contact

052-363-8638

www.linkedin.com/in/or-zarhi



or.zarhi11@gmail.com



https://github.com/orzarhi